wotinspector.com 2019-04-16

# WOTInspector - Privacy Policy

Any service provided by wotinspector.com or it’s apps is subject to this privacy policy. This policy will detail how we store and use the information collected online about you on our websites, during your use of our products and/or services including apps on mobile platforms.

The authors and owners of wotinspector.com are players of the games, we are a very small scale operation. We do value and respect the privacy rights of our users and recognize the importance of protecting the information collected. By using our products and services you consent to the collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information according to the terms of service and privacy policy as it is described in this document.

## 1\. Introduction

Here and below, the authors and owners of the website “wotinspector.com” may be collectively referred to herein as “wotinspector.com”, “we”, or “our”, “the app” or “the service”, when the context requires. “Wotinspector.com” is a developer and publisher of resources, guides, apps and services for the web and mobile devices.

Anyone who has used any of wotinspector.com services or products will be referred to as “You” or “the user”, or other similar words.

By using wotinspector.com websites, applications, or any of the dependent products and services, you signify your agreement to the terms of our Privacy Policy and you state that you understand that wotinspector.com may process your data in accordance with this Privacy Policy. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE FOREGOING, PLEASE DO NOT USE THE SITES OR APPLICATIONS.

Wotinspector.com is independant from Wargaming.net But because wotinspector.com services are dependant on wargaming.net’s own products and services, by using wotinspector.com’s services and products, you are also subject to their terms of service and private policy.

If you access our products and services through a third party, you may be required to also read and accept that third party’s own Terms of Service and Privacy Policy.

Some quick example of typical uses of personal information : when receiving a replay file from you, wotinspector.com may send you a confirmation email containing a link to that replay file. Also, because of the nature of replays and online gaming, players username will appear on these replays when they are published. This is related to wargaming’s own terms of service and is due to the nature of online gaming.

## 2\. Reasons for collecting information

Wotinspector.com collects both personal and non-personal user information, mostly for technical reasons. Personal information is information that may identify you, or may be related to you or your account. Reasons collecting might be:

  * Registration for wotinspector.com and/or other service accounts;
  * User support, contact, and/or technical service requests;
  * User interaction and discussion;
  * Beta test registration, participation or discussion;
  * Contest registration and prize acceptance;
  * Creation of a personal profile;
  * Access to our products and/or services on social networks or other third party services; and
  * Otherwise through normal use of our products, software, mobile or online service where personal information is required for use and/or participation.
  * Creation of a personal profile;

## 3\. Nature of the collected information

Information we may access and collect will vary depending upon the activity and may include your name, email address, in game name or account and platform, server, account or ID related to payments. You can choose not to provide (when such opportunity is provided) certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features.

Information that we don’t need and that we will not ask:

  * land phone number
  * home address
  * birth date
  * mobile phone number
  * credit card information

Non-personal information, alone, cannot be used to identify or contact you. These for exemple includes platform choices as well as many other details. Wotinspector.com collects non-personal information about your use of our online and mobile products and services both on our websites and in the course of game play and software usage. This is for technical reasons, and might be needed to improve the app or service.

Some information may be visible for technical reasons. For example, when you use the services we may be able to read the IP address, but we never personalize the IP addresses, e.g. we can't tell who was using the site or if that user is returning, and we do not collect, store or use it later. So when you use Wotinspector.com online and mobile products and services, we may access certain non-personal information including information about your computer, hardware, OS, software, platform, game system, media, mobile device, including device IDs, incident data, Internet Protocol (IP) address and other information.

When you browse certain portions of the Service, we may automatically collect and record standard user information and clickstream data about your visit (through the use of cookies and otherwise) as part of our analysis of the use of the Service. For example, when you visit or request a web page from our server, we may record the IP address of the user’s machine, the time, date and URL of the request and information about the browser being used, and other information regarding the visit, such as the pages visited on the Service, the time spent on each page, any advertisements clicked and any search terms used (collectively “Log Data”).

When you use any wotinspector.com services or product from a third party, you allow wotinspector.com to access certain information from your profile for that site. The information you allow wotinspector.com to access varies and it is affected by the privacy settings you established with the third party. You can control and find our more about these settings with that third party and not with us. By using a wotinspector.com service, you are authorizing wotinspector.com to collect, store, and use in accordance with this Privacy Policy any and all information that you agreed the third party could provide to wotinspector.com through the third party Application Programming Interface. Your agreement takes place when you “accept” or “allow” or “install”(or similar terms) one of our applications on an third party.

## 4\. Where we store and process your information

Wotinspector.com stores information about you on servers located in the European Union. Personal data collected within the European Union may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Union. Data we collect may also be processed outside the US and the EU, for example when we use a third party service to process information required for wotinspector.com to provide you with the service. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

## 5\. How wotinspector.com uses information collected

Wotinspector.com uses your information only as follows:

  * To provide our products and services to you and fulfill your specific requests;
  * To send you messages about our products and services, new products, features, enhancements, special offers, upgrade opportunities, contests and events of interest;
  * To enable us to discuss with you, receive your messages and contact you back.
  * To enable user-to-user communications;
  * To better understand the behavior and preferences of our users, to troubleshoot technical problems, to deliver advertising, for the purposes of proper functioning of our products and services and improving them;
  * To improve our software and services by providing experiences and recommendations, language and location customization, personalized help and instructions.

## 6\. How we disclose information collected

We disclose your information to third parties, that is parties other than wotinspector.com, in the following circumstances:

  * We may share your information with other services that we own or control which are subject to this same Privacy Policy.
  * From time to time we may employ third party services to collect personal information on our behalf to provide email delivery, advertising, prize or promotional fulfillment, account management, social services, administration, credit card processing, or other services on our sites. We ask some third party contractors, such as credit agencies, data analytics or market research firms, to supplement personal information that you provide to us for our own studies. When our third party agents or service providers collect and/or have access any information other than non-personal, anonymous and/or aggregated data, we then require that they use data consistently, abide to similar privacy policies, and comply with standard practice in place in the industry, particularly that they do not transmit it to anyone else or use it for another purpose or context than our service. These third parties are prohibited from using your personal information for any other purpose without your specific consent.
  * We support and may encourage interaction among players as long as it remains courteous and respectful. Because of the nature of online gaming, your in game name and public messages (such as comments made in game) will be visible at times, for example when a player wants to playback a game in which you appear. He will see your ingame name and the chat messages that you sent. Therefore players may see your name, profile photo and descriptions of your game activity, your game profile. Other players having seen your in game name might also use it to contact you in game or to try to contact you using another service or social media. We cannot avoid this, as it is a consequence of online gaming itself.
  * We may share aggregated information (information about you and other users collectively), anonymous information and certain technical information (including IP Addresses, MAC Addresses for mobile devices and mobile device IDs) to develop our services and deliver targeted advertising in the service and on the websites of third parties. We may also allow advertisers to collect this information within the Service and they may share it with us.
  * We reserve the right to disclose your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, judicial proceedings, court order or other legal process; enforce or apply our Terms of Service and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of wotinspector.com, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and financial risk reduction purposes.
  * In the event that our services undergoes a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, we may transfer all of your information, including personal information, to the successor organization in such transition.

## 7\. Children

Our products and services are not for use or purchase by children and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children. If you are under age of 13, you may use our sites, apps and services only with the consentement and supervision of a parent or guardian. Our purchases are meant to be made by adults only.

## 8\. How does wotinspector.com protect your information?

Wotinspector.com understands the importance of keeping your information safe and secure. Wotinspector.com will make commercially reasonable precautions to protect your personal information and ensure the security of our systems. However, there is no 100% secure method of transmission over the Internet or 100% secure method of electronic storage, especially as technology is continuously evolving. We cannot assume responsibility or liability for unauthorized access to our servers and systems. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer. Chose passwords that are hard to find. Change your passwords often. We strongly recommend that you implement measures to protect your computer from unauthorized access such as firewall protection and anti-virus software.

Also, most of our identification system is based on WGID. WGID is provided as a service by wargaming.net, and wargaming.net identifies you and allows you to log in our services or not. We do not have access to your password for your account with wargaming. Any log in and identification that requires your WGID is made on wargaming side only. 

## 9\. How you can access and update your information

Depending on the service or website, some of your information may be available in an account settings. You can also access, retrieve, correct or update your account information at any time upon manual request. Should you be unable to log in or wish to have your account(s) deactivated, or have any other type of issue, you may send an e-mail to our Support Team at support@wotinspector.com. You can put “Delete my Account” or “Update my information” in the subject line and include your first name, last name, e-mail address and user ID number (if applicable) in the body of the e-mail. We will be happy to review, update or remove information as appropriate. We may still need to retain some of your information in our files however, to resolve disputes, enforce our user agreement, and due to technical and legal requirements and constraints related to the security, integrity and operation of our websites.

## 10\. Changes to our privacy policy

These privacy policy and terms of service are subject to changed at any time. If we decide to make an important change to our Privacy Policy, we will notify you and other users by placing a notice on our apps, website or by sending you a notice to the e-mail address we have on file for you. You should also periodically check this privacy policy page for updates or future reference purposes.
